How are you guys doing today? Welcome to the Hustle zone. I'm your host, Ryan Perez. I mean, it's been a while, and, you know, I was looking at the, you know, the, I we just recently got approved for, IMDb. So it's a movie database where all the, you know, broadcasts, get, you know, documented and data based and, you know, and, and you guys probably seen it because, you know, when you're wanting to read a movie or you want to look up who the cast members are in a movie, you can go on to IMDb and it's pretty much it's like all the credits that are on, it kind of lists all the credits that are in, you know, either, you know, the big screen, the small screen, or any live mini series. And The Hustle is on is a mini series. So, I'm super excited about that, folks. If you guys haven't bought yourself a sweatshirt, tank top, you name it, we got it. So, you know, check us out at Hustle Zone. Dot clothing. That's hustle zone, dot clothing. And that will take you to get that team. And that's where you can, find all of your, hustle zone gear. And pretty much what you're doing is you're supporting the culture, you know, the culture of entrepreneurial ism. We're coining that. That's our thing, you know, that's, because no one has really approached entrepreneurial ism from that, that standpoint. And we we're actually turning this instead of it being called the Hustle Zone. We're going to be calling it hustlers on TV. You can find us on YouTube. You can find us on Vimeo. That's where the Vimeo is going to be, where we we're going to be putting all of our, our, our content. And, folks, this is the first living documentary of entrepreneurs. And we are going to be documenting the culture of entrepreneurial ism. So, you know, give it up for that. You know, I do your clapping over here for the first the first living documentary. And we're going to you'll be able to see this all on Hustle zone.tv. So when we get the website out, when we launch this magazine, we're going to document the culture, the just the essence behind the entrepreneurs that we don't care about. Because here's the thing. People like to crop their success. I like to just remove the crap. I want to see everything because, yeah, you may have money today, but maybe you won't have money tomorrow. But you're still an entrepreneur and nothing changes. You from being an entrepreneur. So we definitely want to highlight that. And then we also want to remove the redundancy because everyone's say the same damn thing. You know, they'll look at air Thomas and look at they'll look at, Grant Cardone, Gary Vee, Zig Ziglar. They will repeat the same stuff over and over again, and it makes the content redundant. So we want to remove the redundancy and actually put some real content talking about the entrepreneur story. So you always know my style, my stance. I start asking I don't go for the direct response. I go for side response. So I go for you know, I've come at these interviews with different angles. So if you are interested in being a writer, please hit me up in my DMs. Please know it is it. It is a commitment, 100% commitment. So I want you guys to, if you are going to commit yourself when you get into the group, there's a lot of information. It's not meant for amateurs or people that are not ready to take it to the next level. It's meant for people that already have their stuff together, and then they just want to add this to their portfolio. You know, because that's how I do business. I don't do business with everybody. And the hustle is always the same nature is that, you know, if you're ready to put content out there, you got your press kit, you got your headshots, you got all that stuff ready. This is the right place for you. So hit me up if you're interested. So, before I get to my guest, I just want to see who's in the room. So who's in the room? No comments right now, which is. Okay. No comments. So we're going to we're going to get right into it. So, episode five, we had, a man by the name of Pierre Evans, and he had come on here to talk about his, his, his life story and how he was caught up in the wrong, you know, caught up in the wrong situations when he was a kid and, you know, and he made some transformations, you know, he lost opportunities with football. And, you know, there's just a lot of things that had happened to him. But then he turned it all around, and now, you know, he started, an organization called Re empower. And, you know, he's been he's been killing it, like I said, every so often, you know, like we're all busy. So we all we all kind of get it when we get it. It's like, hey, what's up? And then we got to go because we're all busy. But you know, he's been killing it. He's been touring. You know, he. And for all those who know Eric Thomas, I mean, Pierre works with them. They're like brothers, man. And it's just nice to see, you know, you know, people on Facebook touching lives of others. So I just want you guys, like, he's in the background, he's laughing and stuff like that. So I just want to get him in. So, what's going on? Just let me my my mouse is not working. What's going on? Pierre? What's going on, man? How are you doing? I'm doing good. I'm doing good, man. So, how how how's life been since last time you been on life? Life's been growing life. Life's been getting better, right? It's, It's not at a standstill, so I have. I have absolutely no complaints with life, man. I'm. I'm enjoying it. You know, I wake up every morning and and I say to myself, I don't know how somebody can be mad or someone can be down or feel a little discouraged. Like you woke up this morning. So just waking up, man, I see a completely different just a true blessing. It just tells me like, yeah, you have another opportunity, right? You have another shot to make today better. If you was mad at yesterday, it's okay. It's over. We got a new beginning. So let's let's make today count. That's awesome. So, can you tell everybody what re empower does and what you guys are all about? Man. Re empower man. It's, you know, it says it all right when you hear Rand Paul was like, okay, Rand Paul Ryan, reinvent yourself. Rand Paul yourself. Readjust. You know, rethink, refocus. Everything that you can put re in front of is what you need to help push your life forward. So for me, you know, just just Rand Paul in itself, I want to the term itself, Rand Paul, when I when we came up with the name of the company, it means to to go back to to that childhood mindset. Right. Like child children are relentless and they go after whatever they want. Like you can tell them no a million times, and they're going to ask you 1,000,001 times. They're going to keep going until they get what they want, and they will not stop. No matter how much you yell at them, no matter how mad you get. Right? I remember I said to my daughter one day, she kept saying, why, why, why? And I kept saying, baby, can you just stop saying why for a minute? And she looked at me. She said, okay, how come? And she switched, right? She she got creative. On another way to ask, she found another way. So Ryan Powers, just go back to that, that mindset of being a child. You know, when you was a child, you asked a million questions a day as adults. Like, we probably went all day long, man. And having asked a question and if you're not asking questions, you're leaving information on the table. And if you're leaving information on a table, you're leaving growth on the table. So that's one of the things, man, you know, Rand Paul is just adding value to your life, not new value, because you already have it. It's just getting you just getting you to look at your life differently and get back to that time in life where you was just gaining all new information daily, and now you stop. And that's the only reason you're not growing is because you are building information. So, can you let the audience know? Because last time we, we talked more about your story, not necessarily about all the great things that you have accomplished. Can you go through, like a Coles notes version of all the things that you guys have done in the, in the last few years? Listen, this here first, first thing. Right, like, you see, you see the paperwork, right? Like you see the paperwork. I want you understand this is this is G-d. You know, reading is not the best. Spelling's not the best. But I took everything from here, and I put it here. And now I want to say, like, the first week of July, the first week of July, the book should be, you know, in my hand, but has been a long time coming. You know, there have been a lot of ups, a lot of downs, a lot of pushbacks. Them sending them back, me sending it back. But it's coming. Right. So that's the, the biggest thing for me is, is the book is complete. It's put down, man, you know, doing doing Canada in, in in September, September 9th and 10th. Well being Toronto and being Winnipeg, you know, I got a call the other day and I'm on a conference call. The beautiful thing about the internet, the internet is a beautiful thing. There's no boundaries. You can cross oceans, you can cross, you know, borders. You can cross whatever you want to cross with the internet. So I just got off a call the other day and to start off the year, maybe I think it's like maybe March, end of March, beginning in April, you know, doing two cities in New Zealand and one in Australia. So it's just constant. It's just constant growing. And I want more than anything, man. I want y'all to understand that the only thing that's getting the company to grow, the only thing that's taking it somewhere different, is the fact that we don't stop. We don't stop, right? Like you run into a brick wall. It's okay. When I run into a brick wall, it says, wow, you traveled some distance, right? Because you wouldn't have a brick wall if there was no distance to travel. If you wasn't moving, you wouldn't be running into a dead end. So every time I run into a dead end, I don't even want to use the term dead end, but a brick wall or, you know, just, you know, something that's that that just tries you. It's a trial and tribulation. It tells me, like, yo, you overcame some things in your life because now you're at a new point. And when you bust through this, you get into a whole nother level. So just seeing levels come down, man, it's just been growing, you know more more towards I'm not have to to call everybody up like, hey, can I come here and speak. Can I come now and speak? There's people now that I try to call and go in for free to speak. And, you know, they didn't want to let me in at first. And now they're calling me and they still want the free drink, right. That that doesn't exist anymore. Right. So it mean the company's just growing and I'm I'm excited to see where it goes in the next, you know, throughout the next two quarters of the year. So what do you think is the the main challenge right now? Because, I mean, we as entrepreneurs, we all have challenges running our businesses and whatnot. Like, what would you say right now is the the major challenge that you're experiencing in all of this quarrying that you're experiencing? Yeah. Just, you know, being being a, a one man team and doing everything on your own. There was a time when I was just looking for help and looking for help and looking for help, and it wasn't coming. And then I got to the point, man, where I said, you know what? I don't want to look for help. I just want to become great at what I do. I just want a master speaking. Right. And I got a ways to go, but that's all I want to work on. So I, I think at some point, at some point as an entrepreneur at least, where I am right now, right, I can only talk where I am. So I'm not I can't go beyond this, beyond where I am, but where I am right now. It's looking for somebody to come in and play the role of some of the roles that I have to play, all of the roles of. But one of the problems that people run into is you've been putting so much of you into this, you've been nursing it. It's your baby. It's like saying, yo, I'm gonna put my two year old on a plane to fly over to, to Guam somewhere, right? And, and fly out the country and all by themselves. And I want I'm going to rely on somebody else to take care of me. So just, you know, at this point, getting someone in, but realizing that when you bring them in, you gotta let it go. You gotta let that part of it go in order for it to grow. Because we spent so much time working, working on working in the company, we don't spend the time we need working on the company. So for me, man, I got, you know, I finally got an assistant. You know, tomorrow we'll have a conversation and we'll talk. But the first thing I said is you do not have to worry about me, you know, trying to micromanage you in and not letting pieces go. I'm putting it. I'm putting it all in your hands. And all I ask is you just give results. So I think that's one of the problems, man. We put so much time into it and then we become afraid to let it go because we want to nurse it. But understand, you can't grow beyond where you are if you don't let things go. And you just work on the things that you're, that you're a master at, right? So just look at it. If you're if you're good at three things, I need you to get rid of two of them. And I need you to just become a master at one. And the other two things I need you to find somebody else to do. And if you master your one, and you allow them to master the one that they're working on, your company will grow at a faster rate. And you you need to stop being nosy and just work on you. Well, yeah. No, I agree with that. And I think that, like, you know, there's two powerful things that I personally believe is like trust and forgiveness. You know, you have to be able to forgive when people make mistakes, and then you have to be able to forgive yourself, but you also have to trust people again. Or and you have to trust people in handing over your baby because, I mean, like, you know, your and especially if it's your first or second, you know, business like it's still emotional or you're emotionally attached to it. But then when you hire an assistant, because I've had a few in, in, you know, in the past few years, it's like I end up doing all the work because I don't want them. I don't want to give them my passwords to my social media account. So how do you feel about all of that, like that level of trust and handing over the keys to somebody and saying, hey, you, you run with it and you know and hope that they bring results back. Like, how do you deal with that? Well, you got it. You got to ask yourself the question, do you want your business to grow or do you want your business to stay where it is? Right. It's it's just that simple. If you want your business to grow, then what you have to do is you have to allow them to grow your business in that area. And if you're not going to allow them to grow your business in that area, then you need to find somebody else. If you don't trust them, why, why why are you working with them? Right. Like just ask you like like, let's just be real. If it's somebody that you don't trust, well, why are you even letting them in what you're doing? They shouldn't even be involved. So you gotta let it go. You gotta ask yourself, right? Just ask yourself. Say. And this is simple and this is why I say, like, all your answers are within you, right? So ask yourself real simple and just say, if I continue on the path that I'm on, am I going to get to the next level? And if the answer is no, then why would you want to keep traveling that path? It means you got to take a shot with somebody. Now that person you get might not be the right one and the next one might not be, and the 10th one might not be. The 11th person might be the one that you need. But because you went through ten bad ones, now you're you're considered to be a bad person, right? It's like they say somebody in domestic violence like, yo, you're battered. Like, now you think everybody in the world is bad and you don't want to talk to nobody. You don't want to trust nobody. Well, it's the same in business. If you had a few bad relationships and it didn't work right now you're running around and you're a bad person. You got to let that go, and you got to rely on somebody. If you want your business to go to the next level. Because if you knew how to do it, you would already be there. You're not there because you're missing something and because you're you, you've been battered and you're in and you feel nervous and you're scared to trust somebody. You will never get to what you want. You're just going to be able to get the thought of what you want to have, but you're not going to get to what you want to have. That's right, that's right. So speaking of which, because this is the hustle zone, and I don't like to do I don't necessarily want to just talk about the elements of success, but I want to kind of mix it in with some current events and currently right now we have, like in youth, you in America have issues with, there's just a lot of drama on the news. And in terms of Donald Trump and, I guess the the issues kind of stem from leadership and being able to trust your leaders in that context with what's happening in the media, like what do you fit like, first off, like, what is your definition of a great leader? May some somebody a leader is somebody who's willing to to do the job themselves and not just look for somebody else to do the job they're willing to lead by example. Right? Because anybody can can have the whole plan down and just manage the plan. But are you going to get your feet dirty, right? Are you going to get your hands dirty? Are you going to be in the trenches? Are you going to are you willing to do the work or are you just looking for somebody to do the work. Right. And that's all fine and dandy. But you know there's there's times when people are going to be nagging at you and saying negative things about your leadership skills. They may not agree with the direction that you want to take. And so where does that come in. And what skill sets do you need to have in order for you to be able to continue to control the situation so that you know, you get to your end goal. You got to you got to be grounded in, in in yourself. Right? You gotta you got to have belief in yourself, in what you do and understand. Every decision you make is not going to be right. There's decisions that I made in my life that aren't right. There's relationships that I that I. Hurt. That that, you know, it wasn't right and it was on me that had the relationship go the wrong way. Right. So there's some things that I know I need to fix relationship wise with some people. Right. So it's from a from a leader standpoint. It's not good. But then I got to ask myself like, yo is what you did? Is it right? It hurt somebody, but is it right? And if the answer is no, then I gotta fix it. If the answer is yes, even if you're mad at me, I gotta stick to what I said, because at the end of the day, I believe that this is going to work. So as a leader, we start looking at, you know, you, the leader of the world. This year, and there's no way that everybody is going to agree with what you do. The most important thing is to make sure that what you do, you believe it's in the best interest of everybody else, and you're not doing it from any, any, dirty way or, you know, you don't have bad intentions. You're just, you know, doing it like, I don't care what happens or I know what's going to benefit me, like what's going to benefit the world. So if you're making decisions based on what's going to benefit the masses, no matter who disagrees, you have to stick with what you're going through because you believe it to work. At the end of the day, if it works, everybody who hating on you, well, everybody who didn't believe it is going to be like, oh my God, it's so great. And they're going to be like, yeah, you know, I, I was I thought it might work. I just wasn't sure. And if it doesn't work, everybody's going to turn on you anyway. So no matter what you do, right. People going to be mad. I just think that you as a person, as a man or as a woman, you have to like, believe in yourself. And if you feel in your heart that it's the best thing to do, listen, follow through with it because no one knows you're going to win or lose until it's over. But most people, what they do is they before they get to it, they start to feel all this pressure coming on and everybody starts to say they've they're pounding on him at all. That's not right. And this ain't right. You should do this and you should do that and that, that beats on you so bad that you do. You change your mind and you make a you make another decision. You second guess your answer on the test. And because you changed it, it's not right. And the teacher calls you up and says, do you? I see you had it right, but you changed it. Why? Hey, Pierre, I just we have to go to a quick commercial break. Just one. We'll be back in one minute. All right. Hey. What's happening? Everybody, coach and be on with coach to guys. And right now, I want to talk to you real quick, man, about the 362 opportunities that you had this year ahead of you. I want you to definitely optimize on those 362 opportunities. Create yourself, have a creative process on what you want to attain this year and be very, very diligent about it. If there's anything I've ever shared with anybody, it's about being diligent and consistent with your desire to be phenomenal for 2017 as well as 2018. So get engaged today and don't waste any more time because despite, despite fear, despite the Hobgoblin, it is time to definitely engage a being great all this year and take every opportunity to the next level. I appreciate your time, coach and beyond. With Coach Augusta, I'm out of here. So yes, we we are back. So I was going to ask you, where do you live? Because you have all this wisdom and knowledge, but where are you? Get it? Like, what are your sources of inspiration right now? Like who are the leaders that you are looking up to? And, or that, that you've, you've met or in the past, you know, who are those people that, you know, ground you? Yeah. For first of all, you know, just just spirit you, man, you know, sticking, you know, being spiritual. It helps me. And I'm not going to tell you I'm the most righteous person in the world. But I do understand there's certain ways you need to live, certain things you need to follow. And, you know, the the mentor that I have right now, Matt, being Eric Thomas and C.J., these are dudes that are not stopping the continuously growing. What happens with a lot of us is we get a mentor that they already stopped growing in their life, and now to a place where they're comfortable and we learn from them. Well, what happens when we surpass them? What happens when we get close to where they are? We get close to their level, whether it's from a intellectual standpoint, a financial standpoint, whatever it is, when we get close to them, most of us don't start the process of looking for someone new. Well, I'm fortunate to work with dudes who are still growing and they're still climbing, and I didn't even learn everything that they learned up until the point where they are. So I'll be following them for for years to come. And you notice I said following, because I find a lot of people have a problem with the term. I don't want to be a follower. Let's be very clear. There's nothing wrong with being a follower. It's just who you decide to follow that becomes the problem. So, you know, outside of outside of Eric Thomas and C.J., you know, Jay-Z and I look at Jay and I study Jay and I read I read up on Jay, you know, not where he is, but we where he was. And I studied the journey and the growth and the transformation. And, you know, he just keeps having. And there was a time when, you know, when Jay came out with the with the first album and it was real street and then he started to grow. Well, he was outgrowing me. Our relationship was becoming distant because his music was based on his growth, but because I wasn't having growth, there was separation. So I was like, Jay wack man want mama listen to do. But as I started to change my life years down the line, many years later, I realized that it wasn't. Jay's music was trash. It was. I wasn't ready to get the information. So what I'm saying to you is sometimes we're watching people where we get the opportunity to study with people and sit with people and get information. But you're getting information from somebody who's out of your league, like, there's so many levels ahead of you that when they're talking to you and giving you information or you're studying information instead of you studying 101, you're studying tool five and you don't even understand 101 yet. So what they're giving you is way over your head and you don't understand it. So you get lost and the growth never comes. You got to stay. You got to respect where you are. First, identify where you are, respect where you are, and find somebody a level two above you. And then you start to study them. And then when you get there, you just keep moving up the chain. So Jay Jay would be the dude that I would say would be that next guy that I look at. You know, I love puffs energy. I love where they come from. I love the fact puff was serving coffee before he got to where he is, and people looking at public puffs. The man, puff was serving coffee. He was up in there as an intern bringing do coffee. Like, whatever you need it. He needs some shoeshine. He bringing his shoes down the street. So when you watch the show we had back in the day when he was sending people to go get cheesecake puffs like, yo, if you think you're too good to go get my cheesecake, I did this already. Right? So, so, so how can you expect me to put you on? And you're not willing to do the stuff that I did to get on? I like I put humility before honor to put me on. And you want to just be on it and you want to get on like, that's not going to happen. So for me, man, watching them dudes and understanding what they been through, where they come from and not just what I see in the media, but reading and studying it, man. So I say, you know, again, Eric Thomas, CK, Jay-Z, puff and and of course, you know, I admire, you know, like like like you're Warren Buffett. I look at him and I'm Buffett buy a company, raise something a penny like, yo, they're selling them. They're selling a million a day. I'm a raise it up a penny. Nobody notices and I make millions more. Yeah, just by doing this. Like bird genius. Gene. Right? Yeah. Straight up. And, like, about the coffee thing. I mean, I started, when I started really learning about management and, running a business. I, I learned from my friend Louise, and we working at a I was, you know, $14 an hour job selling cell phones, and, he, he, he was going to leave the company, and he made me into the manager, but I had to be his assistant, and I was a damn good assistant, which made me a damn good leader. You know what I mean? Because, like, I had to, you know, I had to. I had to make sure I got everything ready for him for these business meetings. But I was so dedicated, making sure everything was right, you know, because there's a lot of us that believe that, you know, just a lot of us believe that we are a specific role. But, you know, being in a team and having a team environment, you know, there's going to be times where you're not the leader and, and, you have to humble yourself to be able to listen to what is happening. You know, because I think John Maxwell was the one. I think a long time ago I was in my early 20s. John Maxwell was like, man, sometimes just go to to meetings, sometimes don't be that one dude in the room that will command the room. It's not it's not your right to step up and be like, well, you know, I'm the man in here and what not your job, because it's obvious that you don't have the ability to lead in that situation. It's not saying that you're not a leader, but you got to be able to be flexible enough to to lead and, you know, to follow. But then also when they don't know and you know, you have to step up and you got to be accountable. Yeah. You know, listen, man, people got to understand like you, you might not be a leader in the room next year in but in another room you're a leader, right. So wherever you are in your life, there's somebody that wants your position. So to the people that want to be where you are, them are the people that you can be a leader to and help them rise up. But you're still going to be a follower in some other room. I don't like it doesn't matter. Right? Like you look at the highest level, like I said, J. So we talk about J. J's a leader, but when Jake gets in the room with buffet, J's humble. Why? Because there's information he's going to get from buffet that he wouldn't get. So he's not the leader in that room, at least not in every discussion. That is discussions that he can lead in. Why? Because he has more of an insight in this area. But the reason people don't understand that is because they don't even know what their strong suit is. They trying to do everything and they trying to do stuff they ain't even great at. They just like doing it. So that's what they want to do, because what happens is you like, so when you're great, when you're great at something or you're good at something and you're on an on the verge of becoming great, the journey gets. Hotter. The things get a lot of rougher, the path gets a lot like the terrain isn't smooth anymore, but it's only rough for a little period. And that period is just testing you to see if you really deserve the attention and the benefits that are going to come when you cross this level of greatness. So if you're not ready and most people back out right there, they back out right there. Like they stop like, man, I don't want to go through that. That's stupid. I'm already good. I'm doing this or, you know, my income's good. Like, my lifestyle is good. Like I'm good, right? Well, man, listen, you're not good with your air. You just don't think you can get the great. So because you don't think you can get to great and you don't believe in yourself enough, you stop. You can't tell me like you've been in the same place for ten years. And this is just where you want to stay. Everybody wants more, but one you don't know how. Number two, when you do get to the point, you're not ready for the test that's in front of you. That's right. I wanted to I just wanted to, acknowledge some of the people in the room. We got some comments. Frank, that's the gusto. Says, know how leaders are the best in the business. Yeah. Damn right. Then we have, Frank again says you need to come with authority and power. No excuses. Lisa Costa says I love John Maxwell. Yeah, he's a great. He's a great leader and a great coach. Lisa says starting from the bottom. So Sean Dell says puff was cleaning toilets. Yeah. That's that's serious. So thank you guys. Frank. Lisa. Sean Dowd, thank you guys. All for,  participating in tonight's discussion. I mean, it's it's always nice. So, folks, don't forget, if you guys want to support the hustles on to continue, to to help us,  get to the next level, we would love for you to purchase a t shirt, a hoodie. It's not to support me and to put food on my kids table. You know, I have a business already. Takes care of that. We just want to get the message out to as many people as possible. We want you also to rep the culture of just, you know, not quitting, you know, so when you're wearing that logo, you're wearing you're wearing something that that means something. Because all of us are volunteering our time just to share this information out with you guys. And, make sure you guys share this podcast. I don't like, you know, I don't ask a lot, because I don't want to bombard you, but, you know, please share. And, you can see that we got six lights. Thank you guys so much for your four loves. Come on, just let it pour. Send this message out to so many people. So now, what, what did you learn here? Like, first, what's your what's your perspective on teamwork? Teamwork, man. You know, I believe that there's a lot of people want a team. Everybody wants to have a team. There's not nobody that doesn't want to have a team. Some people just want a team that only want to do what they say for what they tell them to do. Right? Everybody wants one. But what I what I believe is before you build your team, you have to build yourself to be a one man team. And and I and I don't mean, you know, like, like for a long period of time, but you need to know everything that needs to be done in your business, in your day to day, up until the point that you are that you're currently at. Because when you bring a team in, if you don't know what you need somebody to do, how can you get a team? How can you have somebody come into your team, come into your business, into your life, and you don't even know what role you need them to play? You're just like, oh, I got a team now. Okay, cool. What am I supposed to do? Like, give me a list? You know, like, I don't know, like, let's just build like that. That's not how it works. So, you know, for me, I think a team is you have to first identify the five areas that you're strong in, right? And then once you identify the five areas you're strong in, I think you need to identify the next five areas that you're extremely weak in. And I need you to take out of the five, take the one. And I need you to master that one. And maybe you can play around with two a little bit, but then areas that you're completely weakened, you have to now find somebody who's strong in some areas. But then one of their weaknesses is your strength. And this is what's going to make you a solid team. Because if you just get somebody who's strong in an area you're strong in, and then somebody who's strong in the area that you're okay in, like, that's like you're still you still have weak points. So identify your strengths and your weaknesses. Find somebody who's weakness, who's strength is one of your weaknesses, and bring them to the team, but to one of their weaknesses. Have to be your strength so you can help complement them. And this is what's going to make that chain link fence solid. Well so what. And then so this leads me to the next question is what experiences have you had in working with teams. And you know and take us like take us back to when like were you always a first off. Were you always a team player or did you have situations where you had problems working with others and, and, and whatnot? Because I, I would like everyone to know, you know, because not everybody just walks in teamwork and being like, hey, I'm here for the tape. You know? Yeah, yeah yeah yeah yeah. No, listen, listen, listen. Hey, I could be a team player now because I realized that when I wasn't a team player, it didn't work out too well. Right? So. So, playing this is one of my things, right? So I played basketball at a very young age. I started playing on a team, and it teaches you things. I'm not with this new thing they got, you know, with this sport, everybody gets to be in the game no matter what. Everybody got to get on the field or the team don't. The team can't play or they don't win. I'm not with that. If you don't deserve to be on the field, on the court, then you should not be there. There's no reason I should work extra hard to to create my talent and develop my talent. And you get to get in the game. Like when you're not working at it, you go home and you know you ain't working out. You just eating whatever you want. Like you're like, you're not taking this serious. Well, the bench needs to be where you are. That that just means all you want to do is wear the uniform. You don't really want to be a star on the team. I want to be a star. So I work hard. So as a young guy, you know, playing, playing, playing basketball at the local racks and, you know, I worked hard to play and you had to earn your position on the court. And when I got on the court, there was times I didn't want to pass the ball. I'm the man. I got the ball one on one. I'm going to take you if I make it. Yeah, great. If I don't make it. So what I get you the next time. But I wasn't thinking about my teammates. And I had a great coach and a coach. You said when I would do that, the coach would pull me out and set me on the bench and say, I don't care how good you are, if you don't treat your team right and you don't pass your team, the ball, then you being good by yourself is not good enough for the team. And I'm like, wow. And it took me a long time. Like he benched me a lot of games, a lot of games. He would pull me out and take me out for like a minute or two. Then he got to take me out for a quarter to take me out for half the game. Next thing I know, I'm sitting on the bench. He's like, I'm not playing you today. I'm like, why? He's like, you don't like to pass the ball. So I learn like, okay, let me get my team involved. And I started to see not only was we winning more games, but the chemistry with the team became better. And I said, okay, yep, teamwork. But by the time I got to, you know, playing football as a teenager, you know, that kind of went out the window because you're the only one with the ball. And when you got the ball, it's all about you, right? It's not about anybody else. You get the ball and you run. So I said, if I work extra, extra, extra hard, they're going to be a lot of running plays and I'm gonna get the ball a lot of time and I'm gonna hear my name being yelled out. And I'm going to look real good. But what I didn't realize is that I had to play even when I didn't have the ball. And I, and sometimes I was falling short and my coach called me on it a few times and he benched me. And I said, well, yep, I got to be part of this team. I got to be part of the team thing. So from that point on, that helped me to say, you know what? By myself, I can only take myself so far. I only know so much. I can read a book and you can read a book. I'm getting one thing out of the book. You're getting another thing out. The book. So if I'm not getting what you're getting, that means I'm leaving stuff in the book. So I said to myself, I'm like, okay, cool. As we build business and as we grow, if you put yourself in a group of people who are all looking to get ahead and we're all reading the same thing and studying same the same thing, you're able to give me your feedback. I can give you my feedback. And we got this circle now of code. And because we have the circle of code, we create a winning environment. And I understand like, man, I can't do it by myself. It doesn't matter. We can study the same thing. But that's why some people get it and some people get it f right. Because we're just not studying, right? Right. Yeah. Right. I'm going to just going to take, sorry. I'm going to take,  another jab at these comments here. So, Lisa, Costa says I need a mentor. Well, Pierre is here, guys. So hit up re re empower. What's the website, by the way, up here. RE5 ql.com is real simple r e5 show.com or Pierre Edmunds.com. You can go to a a. It's crazy right? It's crazy. I'd be tripping now. I'd be terrible. So we're we're sitting up in the spot man in the Cheesecake Factory. And, someone came over the came over to E Eric, Eric Thomas. And he was like, yo, man, I heard you do the video on fourth quarter, you know, fourth, the fourth quarter. And he was like, yo, you got to check my man. Fifth quarter living. Oh he got he got the fifth quarter. And it's something completely different. And I'm like yo. Like you got the number one speaker in the world. He's over here like, yo, you got to check out of the fifth quarter. And dude went and checked out. He went and googled fit quarter living and he came up and he was like, yo, I checked out your video in the back, yo, I'm following you from this day on now. No, no, no, I want you to get this right. It's not even about he gave me the plug. It's about he told me a long time ago, like, yo, there's no time for you to get ready. When it's game time. You gotta stay ready. Imagine if I was never posting videos. Imagine if I was never hashtagging fifth quarter living and do go to hashtag and do fifth quarter living and nothing pops up. That means he would have never he would have never been following me. There's something that and it's not even about me, but there's something that maybe he got out of a video that helped him progress in his life, something. So a lot of us are waiting for all of these opportunities, and we're waiting to get all of the money we need to make things happen. And we're not maximizing free. I promise you, you're not maximizing free your life. And the reason you're not is because you're focused on you're you're you're focused on the money you need to make something happen that you're overlooking what you can be doing that's free. It cost me nothing to put the praise to put the, the information in these pages here. This thing cost me nothing, right. It cost me absolutely nothing. So because it didn't cost me nothing, I put it on paper and because I put it on paper and I shared the story, now I got it. Not now. The book is published. I'm going to publish all the books coming out. It didn't cost me nothing to put it there, but because I put my feelings and I put my life on paper, I'm an author and somebody believed in it enough to say, yo, we want to put your book out. Wow. And, I mean, we were just talking about this, prior to the show. Was that, like, even with the Hustle Zone, you know, like, a lot of people commented earlier on like, well, maybe you should do this properly or maybe you should do that. So I'm like, yeah, I got you, I got you, I got you every day with the hustle zone. I'm always trying to do something to improve it, to make it better. But you have to start because it's a if you see an opportunity, there's so much of us that, you know, takes so long to make a decision when we see the opportunity, but we're so quick to like, do things that are not necessarily in our best interest. You know, I don't know why it takes us so long to, to figure out that we're staring in front of, something that can change our life. There's so much cheaper than free resources out there that we can tap, tap into. There's so much people that are willing to work with you if they're if they believe in what you're trying to do. And I think a part of of getting to that next level is that you, you personally have to really, truly believe in what it is that you're doing and believe that you're going to be successful because you're never going to get anything off the ground, whether you have the money or not. See, the the the thing is, is there's people that believe in you more than you believe in you. So because they're believing in you more and you're believing in you, they're fighting harder than you're fighting for you. And by the time you get to the point where you realize that and you're ready to stop fighting the people, that was believing in you are drained the drain. And they're like, yo, you know what? I need you to show me that you really want to do this. I need you to show me that you really want more, and you think like, okay, I was procrastinating for three months, so if I go hard for a week, they're going to be back on my team. If I go home for three months, they're going to go back on my team. No, it might take you two years, three years, four years to show them, like, yo, I'm serious about this and I really want it now. But again, you give up on yourself before you get to the point we like. We bend ourselves so much, right? We bend, but we never. We always stop before we break, before we feel like we're going to break. And the breaking point is so far away you will not break. The only way you're going to break is when you die. When you die is going to be the only time you break. Other than that you're just going to go to some go to like just look at your life. Go look at when you felt the worse. I don't know, maybe your mom passed away. You're your grandmother. You're your, your father who like somebody close to you, somebody passed away and you felt like, man, I don't know how I'm going to live. I don't know how to get past this point. And you're still here. And this was like 30 years ago. It was five years ago. You're still here. So in your mind, that was your darkest moment. But soon as you run into something else, you call this your darkest moment. When are you going to run out of darkest moments? I need you to just. I need you to just say, yo, you know what? I got so much pull in my life that I'm gonna pull myself out of whatever situation I'm in. And I'm going to keep growing. I don't want you to push yourself. I want you to pull yourself because there's more power in the pool than there is in the push. That's right. So, Pierre, we're going to have to get going here. Where can we, where can we find you, man? And he, like I said, man, all social media. Pierre Evans. It would all pop up YouTube channel. Whether it's Facebook, whether it's, you know, Instagram, everything's Pierre Evans. The fifth quarter living movement every Saturday morning is a call. The group, the community's growing. If you're serious about the next level, if you're serious about really, you know, taking your life somewhere different. If you're tired of going through every day and saying, why me? You know what I'm saying? Like, I don't like, let's be done with why me? Like, how me? How can it be me? And let's figure that out. If you're serious about getting somewhere different and growing your life, like reach out to me. Like, listen, I just throw my number out, man, because I'm real big. I believe communication people should have access to you. So. Florido 2021108. And listen, if you're serious about going to the next level, if you're not serious, I'm not the guy to call, right? I don't believe in excuses. But if you're serious about going to the next level, listen, let's do it. Fifth quarter living movement. Like it'll change your life, I promise you. Now, what's the book about and how how will people be able to find it once it's once once you because you're saying it's in the process of being published or it's published right now. Oh, nice. Publish. It's about to hit print. It's about to hit the print screen. So it's all going to be coming up real soon. It'll be everywhere. Everywhere. Amazon. It'll be it'll be all over the place, everywhere. Like you won't miss it. You just Google it and it's popping up. It's going it's going to go crazy. But the book, man, I believe that you can't talk about something if you're not qualified. And I'm not talking about you have the degree. There's a lot of business professors out there that never ran a business, but they're teaching business, right. And I don't get I don't know how that works, but but that one of the qualifications should be you have to have ran a successful business in order to be a business professor. That's in my eyes. Somebody might say, you're wrong, Pierre, but you know the book, it explains my life. It talks about where I was in, you know, some of the tools I used to get to where I am right now. And it's it's the autobiography, and it's just giving you the ins and out. What gives me the right to talk about what I do, what gives me the right to say? I don't want to hear your excuses because it's not worth anything. Like what gives me the right to say that, in the book is going to explain all of that to you, and it's going to give you it's going to give you some solid steps on how to excel in your life. That's awesome. So, you're you're please don't be a stranger, my friend. You're always welcome to come back on the hustle zone when the book drops. Just let me know and then we'll get you on the show. Like, thank you for not, You know, I know that we've been trying, like, it's. I mean, it's been months. It's like every every, every week, you're like, yo, man, I want to get back on. I want to get back on. So, you know, we finally got you back, and this was a blessing. Thank you so much. Pierre, for for coming into the house is also, you know, the tradition. You know, I'm going to do a call response. I'm going to say, welcome to the. And then you're going to have to scream,  hustle zone as loud as you can, my brother. So yeah, let's go to the hustle zone. Yes, sir. Awesome, awesome. Well thank you. Thank you so much, my brother and folks. Man, you guys really need to check out,  Pierre Evans. Man. Like, he's so motivational every time he comes on here, it's it's just a treat. And, you know, he has. He does his live broadcasts. I mean, he does his video productions. Video production is on point, man. You know, he he's pretty much it. It's like, if there's anyone that you want to learn from, he's the guy. Because, you know, he's seen both sides of the coin. You know, it's like you got, you know, you got people that are coaches that have never really experienced, you know, a whole lot. They just go to school. They get the the course. They learn how to motivate and they learn how to kind of get people going along. But then you have guys like Pierre that, you know, have real experiences of just dealing with life and then and then and now they're there and, and his experiences are so relevant that he and every time he talks to somebody, people like they're he's thinking what I'm thinking. He understands where I'm coming from. So that is the benefit of of checking, Pierre Evans out, you know, and and, and even checking out some of the people that he's associated with, I mean, Eric Thomas, man. Like, that's, it, man, like, we,  we are all watching his videos on YouTube. Like, these are great people that he's associated with, but he's carved a name for himself. He's done it himself. Just by persevering and offering great leadership, you know, and, you know, being an example, a good example, you know, and like I would say is a you don't have to be a great example. You don't have to be a bad example, but just be a good one. And for sure, Pierre Evans is a good example. So it's always a pleasure. He's always welcome to come back on the show, folks. Hustler magazine is coming soon. We got the team ready. I had to remove people from the group. Not that I hate you. I just want to say now, I don't hate any of the people that I had to remove is just that we're looking for active participants. So if you're a writer and you're ready to take things to the next level, and you want to be shown on to the hustle zone, there's four things you gotta do. You gotta have your headshots. You have to have your headshots done, by somebody else, not by your iPhone. You need to get your, we have release forms and agreements for disclosures that you have to sign. You have to fill in the application so that we have all your, your, your links to your social media and, and whatnot, so that when we do post your article that we have all the proper representation, and then you send us a logo so that we can we can, we can advertise your company and whatnot. And pretty much the hustler magazine is there to put you out to make you better. We're not trying to replace motivational brands, you know, and coaching. We're not doing any of that stuff. We're just amplifying what you're already doing. On a platform. And we we care about design. We care about presentation. We care about just how it's delivered so that people can really understand the true essence of your story. So please hit me up if you're interested in being a writer. But please understand that if you're doing business with me, I am a straight shooter, but I'm very detailed. I have systems in place, and you've got to be able to catch up. And if you can't catch up, get someone that can help you catch up. You know, like I had one person, it I had one person. He has an office manager. Went and filled out the application. Like, if you can't do it, get someone else to do it, you know, so that you're ready to, you know, to be published. Because I'm putting people on IMDb, you know, I'm putting people I'm actually going to, you know, to the like, I'm doing this at 120%, getting everybody, you know, maximum exposure. And I'm putting my own money into it. So I'm not going to be half step. And it's not okay to get someone else to do your headshots. So, are not it's not okay for you to do your own headshots. You really got to take it seriously. So thank you guys so much,  for participating in the hustle zone. And, until next time, I'm going to put these credits here. And sepia is already. You see these stars? Pierre is already. In the credits. The credits were created. This is awesome. You know, we're venturing on some technology. That y'all don't have access. Yet, so you guys want to make sure you check out the hustle Zone. So I love you guys so much. Have a good one.